Sniper: Ghost Shooter is a action, drama, war film directed by Don Michael Paul.
Elite snipers Brandon Beckett and Richard Miller are fighting extremists in the Middle East when the Colonel gives them a new mission: to
protect a gas pipeline stretching from the Republic of Georgia to Western Europe from extremists eager to make a political statement.
But when skirmishes with the enemy lead to U.S.
snipers being killed by a ghost shooter who locks into their
exact location, a security breach is suspected.
Fingers are pointed and battle lines are drawn, all
leading up to an explosive climax.
Brandon Beckett, played by Chad Michael Collins.
Richard Miller, played by Billy Zane.
Cervantes, played by Nick Gomez.
Andrei Mashkov, played by Ravil Isyanov.
Robin, played by Stephanie Vogt.
Mothershed, played by Navid Negahban.
Sniper: Ghost Shooter is a 2016 American direct-to-video action film.
The film is the sixth installment of the Sniper film
series and a sequel to Sniper: Legacy (2014).
The film explores themes of sniper, mission, gas, gun, shooter.
The tone is emotional.